http://www.weonlydo.com/index.asp?privacy=1

Privacy statementLast updated: January 19, 2017
Personal Information:
At WeOnlyDo! Software, we are
committed to protecting your privacy however we may ask you to provide us with
information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). This
statement of privacy explains data collection and use in those situations that
we require Personal Information. Please read the complete WeOnlyDo! Software
Privacy Statement.
Collecting Your Personal
Information:We will ask you when we need
Personal Information. For example, we may request Personal Information when you
download evaluation software, email us, request an License Key or ask us to
forward product information to you.
Use of Your Personal
Information:We use your Personal
Information for four primary purposes:
To make the site easier for a
you to use by not making you enter your Personal Information more than once.
To allow you to purchase
and/or download products.
To gather broad demographic
information about user trends and visitors to our website.
To enable WeOnlyDo!
Software, our resellers and distributors to alert you to product upgrades,
special offers, updated information and other new services from WeOnlyDo!.
We may occasionally hire
other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging,
mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or
services and sending postal mail. We will only provide those companies the
information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using
that information for any other purpose.WeOnlyDo! Software will
disclose your Personal Information, without notice, only if required to do so by
law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary: (a) to conform to
the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on WeOnlyDo! Software
or the site; (b) to protect and defend the rights or property of WeOnlyDo!
Software, (c) to act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of
users of WeOnlyDo! Software, its web site or the public, or (d) in connection
with a merger or the sale of all or substantially all of WeOnlyDo!'s business or
assets.
Control of Your Personal
Information:When you register, or
otherwise give us Personal Information, WeOnlyDo! Software will not share the
Personal Information with third parties without your permission, other than for
the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes as
stated above.WeOnlyDo! Software may
request selected third parties to send you information about their products or
services. When you provide WeOnlyDo! Software with your Personal Information,
you will be able to decline to receive correspondence from WeOnlyDo! or such
third parties. To request not to receive correspondence please write or email to
info@weonlydo.com.
If you choose not to provide
Personal Information, you may still use our web sites anonymously. Only the
domain name from which you access the Internet, the Internet address and the
date and time you access our web sites are logged. WeOnlyDo! Software uses this
information to analyze trends and to measure the number of visitors to our
sites.
Online Purchases:When you submit an order
on-line, your credit card number is submitted to the credit institution for
routine processing. WeOnlyDo! Software does not collect your personal credit
history information and does not share credit or credit card information.
Access to Your Personal
Information:You may request to review and
update your Personal Information at any time by contacting WeOnlyDo! Software at
info@weonlydo.com and request to see the
Personal Information details WeOnlyDo! Software has collected. Note, that all
Personal Information that WeOnlyDo! holds has been given to WeOnlyDo! Software
by you. WeOnlyDo! has not collected Personal Information about you from any
other source.
Security of Your Personal
Information:WeOnlyDo! Software strictly
protects the security of your Personal Information and honors your choices for
its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized
access or disclosure, alteration or destruction.Your Personal Information is
never shared outside WeOnlyDo! Software without your permission, except under
conditions explained above. Inside WeOnlyDo! Software, data is stored in
password controlled servers with limited access.
Linked Websites:WeOnlyDo! Software 's
websites may include links to the web sites of others. However, WeOnlyDo!
Software is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these
linked sites.
Use of Cookies:Some of our web pages use
"cookies". A cookie is a small file that a web site instructs a browser to place
on your hard drive. Note that a cookie does not contain any Personal
Information. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, but if you do, you
might not be able to take full advantage of our site.
Changes to this Statement:WeOnlyDo! Software will
occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the
"last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to
this statement, WeOnlyDo! Software will notify you by placing a prominent notice
on the web site.
Questions/Comments:If you have concerns or
comments about WeOnlyDo! Software's Privacy Policy and related practices, or you
would like WeOnlyDo! Software not to provide your Personal Information to
carefully selected companies or you would like to stop receiving information
from WeOnlyDo! Software or its resellers, or you want to correct or update your
Personal Information: Contact WeOnlyDo! Software either by emailing us at
info@weonlydo.com or by calling us at any
one of our WeOnlyDo! offices.
I really like these products - they are consistently first rate! David WittenWWR Development, Inc.
We have recently completed a large 1200+ location project where reliable Telnet and SSH connectivity was required. wodSSH worked flawlessly and allowed our staff to complete our project ontime and within budget.James SieversHarbor Technologies
Congratulations on an excellent product and first rate support!Sander PoolRhapsody Networks
...your service has been phenomenal.
It's always quick and you are there when I need you.James NewmanCastleberry Investments
We have recently completed a large 1200+ location project where reliable Telnet and SSH connectivity was required. wodSSH worked flawlessly and allowed our staff to complete our project ontime and within budget.James SieversHarbor Technologies
...what I really like is that wodSSH and wodSFTP components work excellently and are constantly being improved...Steven JonesSABIEN project
Your customer service was excellent, and I will look at your products in the future for precisely that reason. Charles TaylorInterWeave, Inc.
Just thought you'd like to know that my gateway app with your SMTP Server component held the line against a DDOS attack today... Chris LangsenkampClever Technologies
...with a minimum of effort as the DLL interface was written with such simplicity...Zack MenendezMapframe Corporation
Your professionalism is reflected into your email, your product and your web site. I am confident that these will make the difference. Sylvain PaquetteR&D Analyst at InfoPharm Inc.
